# RANDY PANOPIO

randypanopio.github.io randypanopio@gmail.com 778 - 926 - 8693 Vancouver, B.C

I am a design oriented developer with a focus on building usable and maintainable tools. With a diverse background of user experience and web development, to cinematography and physical art. I try to bridge ideas and build sustainable products in all of the projects that I partake in.

## **Skills**

### **Development**

Languages: C#, .NET, Python, Java Tools: Powershell, NodeJS, Docker Web: JS, PHP, Angular, Django Version Control: Git, Perforce, GitHub RESTful API integration

#### **Content Creation**

Adobe Suite (Photoshop) 3D Modeling (Maya, Blender) Character Rigging FK/IK Animations Vector and Raster Graphics

#### **Toolkit**

Maya Scripting (MayaPy, PyMEL) Unity Engine & Tooling Procedural Content Generation Shaders (Shader Graphs) Frostbite Engine

## Methodologies

Test Driven Development, Agile Methodology, Iterative Design Process, Pipeline Architecture Design, User Research Methodology

## **Education**

#### **Simon Fraser University**

Interactive Arts and Technology (SIAT), Bachelor of Science -Concentration of Interactive Systems

2015 - 2020

## **Work Experience**

## Electronic Arts Associate Technical Artist

Burnaby, British Columbia **Sept 2021 - Present** 

Worked on pipeline tool development and management to deliver art assets from content creation to in game render. Supported multiple FIFA/FC titles including titles from 22, 23, the FC rebrand, FIFA Online, FIFA Mobile, and unreleased incubation football titles.

- Subject matter expert on content management and worked on designing and replacing the delivery pipeline, tripling the previous workflow's throughput and reducing process runtime from a 10 minute run down to 1 minute, while introducing previously unsupported content into this automated framework. Supporting over a hundred thousand unique files and assets per year.
- Improved and automated legacy pipelines, saving the team workflow capacity by up to 75% by eliminating manual workflows with automated pipelines, saving team members several hours during a typical work week.
- Collaborated and supported cross domain teams and multiple international teams to organize, process, and deliver content into the game while maintaining production timelines.
- Updated existing DCC tools and authored new tools to improve and automate repetitive tasks from artists and management, while training and supporting them with our production workflows and tools.

# Under the GUI Academy Inc. **Programming Instructor**

Richmond, British Columbia
Dec 2020 - June 2021

Taught children ages 7 - 16 concepts of programming through hands on Unity and website projects during weekly online class sessions.

- Introduced concepts regarding programming foundations, web development, and game design to children with various skill levels
- Volunteered creating personalized coding challenges for advanced students who showed interest in expanding their programming repertoire

# Safe Software Inc. Front-End Web Developer - Co-op

Surrey, British Columbia May 2018 - Dec 2018

Acted as a front-end developer and the primary interface designer, maintaining and building web interfaces for a suite of enterprise GIS management tools.

- Collaborated with a team of developers, product managers, and stakeholders working on a new core feature, on an enterprise web application used by over 10,000 organizations across the world
- Implemented three new UI for new features built upon existing management tools with over 100 individual UI elements within 3 design iterations, and completed the testing phase within 4 months.
- Worked in an agile and test-driven development environment, building upon a hybrid web framework application while authoring and maintained unit tests during production